{
    "subject": "resource/Fazal_Malik_Akif",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Khyber_Pakhtunkhwa",
    "human_readable": "Fazal Malik Akif was born in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9304159879684448,
            "question": "Where was Fazal Malik Akif born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6560431122779846,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about people born in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6099237203598022,
            "question": "What is Khyber Pakhtunkhwa known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5951834321022034,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Fazal Malik Akif?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4998243451118469,
            "question": "What is the history of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42860570549964905,
            "question": "What are some famous landmarks in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3811476230621338,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3452876806259155,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3334525227546692,
            "question": "Are there any interesting traditions or festivals celebrated in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3317376375198364,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by people living in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fazal Malik Akif was born in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7419_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any interesting traditions or festivals celebrated in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7419_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7419_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7419_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7419_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The text does not mention where Fazal Malik Akif was born. It only mentions that he (Urdu: \u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0645\u0627\u0644\u0643 \u0639\u0627\u06a9\u0641\u200e) (born 22 October 1947) is a Pakistani singer and songwriter, but it does not provide information about his birthplace within Pakistan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about Fazal Malik Akif's place of birth. While there is a mention of Fazal Malik Akif, it does not include his date or place of birth, making it impossible to confirm the statement that he was born in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Fazal Malik Akif is a Pakistani singer who gained popularity in the 1970s, and there is no information provided that suggests he was born in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on Afghan refugees in Pakistan and Pakistani culture, with no mention of Fazal Malik Akif or Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Province.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no information about Fazal Malik Akif's birthplace in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The given context does not mention Fazal Malik Akif's birthplace. Therefore, there is no information to support the statement that he was born in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}